Hello everyone friends, if you
drive any vehicle on the road, drive a car, ride a bike, then it is
very important for you to have insurance for it and you do not know
that insurance is also available through FunPe, then
I am going to tell you about it, yes
friends, whether it is a car or a bike, you can get
insurance for this thing here, you can also get life insurance,
you can also get health insurance, that too
through Paytm, that too within 30 seconds,
however, in today's video
I will tell you how you
can get car insurance, by
following the same steps that I will tell you for the car,
you can do it for the bike as well, you can also get health
insurance, you can also do SMS, so
let's learn today
how to get insurance for the car through FunPe, so
friends, here I have opened my FunPe,
you have to open this FunPe application
first and here this
is the home page, on the home page itself you have to
scroll down a little, then here you will
find a section with insurance, where  It is
written Bike Car Health, which means
you can get any insurance you want from here,
I have to click on
Car here because I want to get car
insurance, so I click on Car,
friends, if you have already
taken any insurance, then you should
see below, I have taken it, it is
showing me below in Active, if you have
not taken it, then you will simply
click on the Insurance Under Car option,
so here you will get the option of entering the car number, the
number of the vehicle,
you have to simply click on the
option of Enter Your Private Car Number here,
you have to enter your car number here, so first of all I
enter my car number here,
I have entered the car number here,
simply there is a submit button here, you also have to
click on submit and I also have to
click on submit, let me click,
as if I have clicked here on
submit, the car number is coming up, which
vehicle is this, it is also telling which name is there,
when was it registered, which
scheme is there, it is also telling  It is telling here that 2018
and here you have been given three options to
select, first of all
what do you use the car for, that is,
you are driving your car for personal use,
your car comes, you are using it in taxi,
you have to give that here, mine is
personal, I will keep the personal one only, second
what is your previous policy type, your
earlier policy was
Infensia third party, you have to
select that here, I will select third party,
my third party was yours, if it is
comprehensive then you can
select that and third here it is asking has
your previous policy expired, that means your
previous policy is Infensia, has it expired,
if it has expired then
you have to click on yes, if it has
not expired then there are three left, yours is about to
expire then you have to click on no, if
mine is about to expire then
I want to renew it, then I
will click on no, if yours has already
expired then you have to click on yes,
now you have to see below  Simply you
get the option of view plans, you have to simply
click on view plans, as soon as you
click on view plans, it will suggest
which insurances are available for your vehicle
which you can do here,
you will get to see a lot of insurance here
and the price will also be visible
but before doing insurance, keep one
thing in mind, there are two types of insurance,
one is third party and the other is
comprehensive, the price
of third party is very less, it means
what happens in third party is that if
by chance something happens to your vehicle, then
nothing of your vehicle will be recovered there,
you will not get the benefit for making an insurance claim
there, but if
your car collides with someone and
some other person gets injured or the
car gets damaged, then
if you clean it, then everything will be
compensated there, you will not be compensated,
that happens in third party and
what happens to you in compensation is that your loss
and the loss of the other person, all are made up there, so if
you do this thing  If you want to
learn in Bikel, then tell me in the comments below,
I will make a video. I have to take
third party here, so there
is a plan option above here, I have to click on it and make it third
party and as soon as I
do third party, the
price of the insurance will reduce even more, you can see,
many insurances have been suggested here, the
price of which is showing 94, so
simply you have to decide here,
whatever insurance you have, I am going to make it with National
Insurance, so I will
click, this will fetch and you will have to
enter the owner details here i.e. your name, complete mobile number, email address etc.
and if you scroll down completely here, then
you will also have to enter the PAN card number and date of birth below, so
let me enter the PAN card and my date of birth,
I have
also entered my PAN card number, date of birth here
and above here I have entered the name, mobile number and
email address, I will blur it,
I am explaining to you, you should understand, I will do it
in blur because this is my private
information, here you will find a
continue button below.  You get it, you have to simply
click on continue, then it is
possible that this type of option will come in front of you where
your previous policy number will be asked,
your policy expiry date, then it is
possible that there is an option of previous policy in front of you
where you will be asked
when your previous policy expired, you will be asked to
select the date here,
if you are not sure
when was my date, that is, when did it expire, then there is
a button above I don't remember
previous policy details, you have to click on it, it will
completely close and
below you will get a continue button, you have to
click on continue, now as soon as you
click on continue, the complete
details etc. will come where there will be your vehicle
number, chassis number, engine number
and which insurance is it, it will be
told to you and whether it is third party or not, it will
also be told to you here, it will be
told here that mine is one year third party only, the
price will be shown to you below, mine is showing ₹ 71, it
may increase further, so mine is shown
here  It is showing ₹ 71, okay, so
simply click on it, exclusive
of GST, click on it, then the details will come up as to
where you are spending your money,
in this insurance is ₹ 4 and
GST is ₹ 77, totaling ₹ 471 you will have to
pay, so to make the payment simply
click on Buy Plan, as soon as
you click on Buy Plan,
all your accounts will appear,
select the account from which you want to make the payment
and there is a Pay button below,
click on Pay, after clicking on Pay,
your UPI option will come up there,
enter the PIN to enter the DI PIN, click on Done, the
payment will be done, after the payment is done,
your interface will be successfully done, where
if you click on this button, then
all the details will come to you and from there
you will get a download button, by
clicking on that download button you
can download your PDF which is the insurance file, which you can
photocopy  You can keep a print of it and if you want, you
can keep it in your mobile also, so that you will
not face any problem if you go somewhere
and if the people from PIL trouble you by asking you to
show this insurance, then you
can save yourself by showing it,
you will not face any problem, so this is how the incident is done
through PhonePe,
if you liked this video
then do like the video
and also subscribe to the channel, so that
whatever information I have given you, if
you liked it then you
must subscribe, I will meet you in the next video, till then take
care of yourself, Jai Hind Vande Mataram